export const questions = [
  {
    question: "ii of C",
    answers: ["Am", "Fm", "Gm"],
    correct_answer: "Am",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of C",
    answers: ["Am", "Em", "Bm"],
    correct_answer: "Em",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of C",
    answers: ["F", "G", "A"],
    correct_answer: "F",
  },
  {
    question: "V of C",
    answers: ["G", "C", "D"],
    correct_answer: "G",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of C",
    answers: ["Am", "Dm", "Em"],
    correct_answer: "Am",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of C",
    answers: ["Bdim", "Fdim", "Gdim"],
    correct_answer: "Bdim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of G",
    answers: ["Am", "Em", "Bm"],
    correct_answer: "Am",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of G",
    answers: ["Bm", "F#m", "Em"],
    correct_answer: "Bm",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of G",
    answers: ["C", "D", "E"],
    correct_answer: "C",
  },
  {
    question: "V of G",
    answers: ["D", "A", "E"],
    correct_answer: "D",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of G",
    answers: ["Em", "Am", "Bm"],
    correct_answer: "Em",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of G",
    answers: ["F#dim", "C#dim", "D#dim"],
    correct_answer: "F#dim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of D",
    answers: ["Em", "Bm", "F#m"],
    correct_answer: "Em",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of D",
    answers: ["F#m", "C#m", "G#m"],
    correct_answer: "F#m",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of D",
    answers: ["G", "A", "B"],
    correct_answer: "G",
  },
  {
    question: "V of D",
    answers: ["A", "E", "B"],
    correct_answer: "A",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of D",
    answers: ["Bm", "Em", "F#m"],
    correct_answer: "Bm",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of D",
    answers: ["C#dim", "G#dim", "A#dim"],
    correct_answer: "C#dim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of A",
    answers: ["Bm", "C#m", "D"],
    correct_answer: "Bm",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of A",
    answers: ["C#m", "D", "E"],
    correct_answer: "C#m",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of A",
    answers: ["D", "E", "F#m"],
    correct_answer: "D",
  },
  {
    question: "V of A",
    answers: ["E", "F#m", "G#dim"],
    correct_answer: "E",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of A",
    answers: ["F#m", "G#dim", "A"],
    correct_answer: "F#m",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of A",
    answers: ["G#dim", "A", "Bm"],
    correct_answer: "G#dim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of E",
    answers: ["F#m", "G#m", "A"],
    correct_answer: "F#m",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of E",
    answers: ["G#m", "A", "B"],
    correct_answer: "G#m",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of E",
    answers: ["A", "B", "C#m"],
    correct_answer: "A",
  },
  {
    question: "V of E",
    answers: ["B", "C#m", "D#dim"],
    correct_answer: "B",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of E",
    answers: ["C#m", "D#dim", "E"],
    correct_answer: "C#m",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of E",
    answers: ["D#dim", "E", "F#m"],
    correct_answer: "D#dim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of B",
    answers: ["C#m", "D#m", "E"],
    correct_answer: "C#m",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of B",
    answers: ["D#m", "E", "Gb"],
    correct_answer: "D#m",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of B",
    answers: ["E", "Gb", "G#m"],
    correct_answer: "E",
  },
  {
    question: "V of B",
    answers: ["Gb", "G#m", "A#dim"],
    correct_answer: "Gb",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of B",
    answers: ["G#m", "A#dim", "B"],
    correct_answer: "G#m",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of B",
    answers: ["A#dim", "B", "C#m"],
    correct_answer: "A#dim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of Gb",
    answers: ["Abm", "Bbm", "Cb"],
    correct_answer: "Abm",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of Gb",
    answers: ["Bbm", "Cb", "Db"],
    correct_answer: "Bbm",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of Gb",
    answers: ["Cb", "Db", "Ebm"],
    correct_answer: "Cb",
  },
  {
    question: "V of Gb",
    answers: ["Db", "Ebm", "Fdim"],
    correct_answer: "Db",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of Gb",
    answers: ["Ebm", "Fdim", "Gb"],
    correct_answer: "Ebm",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of Gb",
    answers: ["Fdim", "Gb", "Abm"],
    correct_answer: "Fdim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of Db",
    answers: ["Ebm", "Fm", "Gb"],
    correct_answer: "Ebm",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of Db",
    answers: ["Fm", "Gb", "Ab"],
    correct_answer: "Fm",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of Db",
    answers: ["Gb", "Ab", "Bbm"],
    correct_answer: "Gb",
  },
  {
    question: "V of Db",
    answers: ["Ab", "Bbm", "Cdim"],
    correct_answer: "Ab",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of Db",
    answers: ["Bbm", "Cdim", "Db"],
    correct_answer: "Bbm",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of Db",
    answers: ["Cdim", "Db", "Ebm"],
    correct_answer: "Cdim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of Ab",
    answers: ["Bbm", "Cm", "Db"],
    correct_answer: "Bbm",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of Ab",
    answers: ["Cm", "Db", "Eb"],
    correct_answer: "Cm",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of Ab",
    answers: ["Db", "Eb", "Fm"],
    correct_answer: "Db",
  },
  {
    question: "V of Ab",
    answers: ["Eb", "Fm", "Gdim"],
    correct_answer: "Eb",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of Ab",
    answers: ["Fm", "Gdim", "Ab"],
    correct_answer: "Fm",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of Ab",
    answers: ["Gdim", "Ab", "Bbm"],
    correct_answer: "Gdim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of Eb",
    answers: ["Fm", "Gm", "Ab"],
    correct_answer: "Fm",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of Eb",
    answers: ["Gm", "Ab", "Bb"],
    correct_answer: "Gm",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of Eb",
    answers: ["Ab", "Bb", "Cm"],
    correct_answer: "Ab",
  },
  {
    question: "V of Eb",
    answers: ["Bb", "Cm", "Ddim"],
    correct_answer: "Bb",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of Eb",
    answers: ["Cm", "Ddim", "Eb"],
    correct_answer: "Cm",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of Eb",
    answers: ["Ddim", "Eb", "Fm"],
    correct_answer: "Ddim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of Bb",
    answers: ["Cm", "Dm", "Eb"],
    correct_answer: "Cm",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of Bb",
    answers: ["Dm", "Eb", "F"],
    correct_answer: "Dm",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of Bb",
    answers: ["Eb", "F", "Gm"],
    correct_answer: "Eb",
  },
  {
    question: "V of Bb",
    answers: ["F", "Gm", "Adim"],
    correct_answer: "F",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of Bb",
    answers: ["Gm", "Adim", "Bb"],
    correct_answer: "Gm",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of Bb",
    answers: ["Adim", "Bb", "Cm"],
    correct_answer: "Adim",
  },
  {
    question: "ii of F",
    answers: ["Gm", "Am", "Bb"],
    correct_answer: "Gm",
  },
  {
    question: "iii of F",
    answers: ["Am", "Bb", "C"],
    correct_answer: "Am",
  },
  {
    question: "IV of F",
    answers: ["Bb", "C", "Dm"],
    correct_answer: "Bb",
  },
  {
    question: "V of F",
    answers: ["C", "Dm", "Edim"],
    correct_answer: "C",
  },
  {
    question: "vi of F",
    answers: ["Dm", "Edim", "F"],
    correct_answer: "Dm",
  },
  {
    question: "vii° of F",
    answers: ["Edim", "F", "Gm"],
    correct_answer: "Edim",
  },
];
